Kettle and Idol
Second.
Yes.
Comedy.
I love it so much that I go to a comedy concert at least once a month.
Is that so?
Yes, I do.
Is there a theater in Fukuoka?
A theater opened in Fukuoka two years ago.
I didn't know that.
But you had to go to Osaka or Tokyo to see it.
I was like, "Oh, you had to go all the way to Osaka or Tokyo to see it?
But now that the theater was established in Fukuoka two years ago, something in me was off,
But now that Fukuoka opened two years ago, something in me has been removed,
I can go as much as I want.
I want to go there.
Yes, I want to go. I want to go.
It's fun to watch.
It is the time for silk.
So, even when I can't make it to Tokyo or Osaka, or when I go there on business,
I check the schedule.
I always ask, "Geisha, which theater is playing today?
Oh, really?
When I come to Tokyo, I also check various theaters in Tokyo,
I also check the schedule when I come to Tokyo. I'm glad to know that you're out there.
I'm happy to know that they are appearing.
Like Shibuya, Shibuya.
Oh, no...
But it makes me happy.
Do you have any recommendations for comedians?
My favorite comedian in Tokyo right now is Reiwa Roman.
Yes, yes.
In Osaka, I like Cherry Daisakusen.
Cherry Daisakusen.
Heh~
He's funny.
Very interesting!
I'm the type of person who starts with a story,
I often watch all of the M-1 Grand Prix from the first round.
That's great.
In Tokyo, there is Reiwa Roman.
What about you, Mr. Reiwa Roman?
Yes, he is.
What do you think of him from a writer's point of view?
Which idol likes you, Mr. Reiwa Romain?
Mr. Reiwa Romain.
I think she's a little bit out of the ordinary, so I think she really digs him.
I am digging.
Thank you very much.
Do you feed that back into your own activities?
Is it just for fun?
I'm just hoping to get a little bit of that into my MCing and stuff like that.
I see.
Yes, I do.
So, for example, well, well, well,
If I were in your position, I might not be able to say so strongly,
If I were in your position, I might not be able to say so strongly, but if I were to include a live comedy show produced by Rico,
What would you do?
What if I were to book it?
You mean, I'll see it, I'll see it?
I would see it.
I produce the show and let the audience see it.
So I'm looking at it from the customer's point of view.
Regardless of whether it's an application or not?
No, but it's totally fine to think for yourself.
My favorite comedian is Wagyu, so I want to invite Wagyu.
Laughing rice.
This is a bit..,
What do you think?
A bird.
Or a bird. A little bit of order.
Order?
I would like to have Laughing Man as the last performer and Wagyu before him.
And, of course, the top batter,
I'd like to go with Mr. Reiwa Roman,
I'd like to go with Mr. Reiwa Romain.
Oh, Mr. Reiwa Roman is the top batter.
Next,
Double Azuma-san, right?
Double Higashi-san. Katakana.
Double Higashi-san.
I'm sorry. I'm an uninformed person who's looking at this.
I knew you existed, too,
I saw you live for the first time this past March,
Yes, I did.
It was really interesting.
I think I was still aware of it,
Was it at a theater like Yoshimoto's in Shibuya?
Osaka.
Kyoto.
That's great.
Kyoto month?
Gyeongsing month.
In Gyeongsangetsu.
I traveled there just to watch comedy.
That's how much I like it,
Let me tell you about my dream of producing myself. Customer.Let me also say dream self-production. Customer.
Yes.
So, during the last part,
I'm going to be in Osaka for a while,
Karashikon-san.
Oh, that's great.
It's like a dream, isn't it? This is like a dream.
Yes, it is.
I want to be at the front of the line.
Well, it's very important for me to know that.
It's very important for me to know that in this job.
Courtesy of my refrigerator.
Thank you very much.